{
    "subject": "resource/One_Mysterious_Night",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1940s_crime_films",
    "human_readable": "One Mysterious Night is about 1940s crime films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6905636787414551,
            "question": "How might social issues of the 1940s be reflected in 'One Mysterious Night'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6006842255592346,
            "question": "How has the genre of crime film evolved since the 1940s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5595283508300781,
            "question": "What type of films are associated with the 1940s era?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5146746635437012,
            "question": "Are there any famous directors known for making crime films in the 1940s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44525372982025146,
            "question": "What decade is the film 'One Mysterious Night' set in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3104228973388672,
            "question": "What genre does the film 'One Mysterious Night' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3072025179862976,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of a popular film from the 1940s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3068099915981293,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in crime films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2265750765800476,
            "question": "What elements are typically found in crime films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1719352900981903,
            "question": "What makes a good crime film suspenseful?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=One Mysterious Night is about 1940s crime films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5987_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What elements are typically found in crime films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5987_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in crime films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5987_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give me an example of a popular film from the 1940s?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5987_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_168.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5987_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context discusses the 1940s as a period rich with influential mystery and crime films, including specific examples like \"The Maltese Falcon\" (1941), which falls under the category of crime films. This information supports the statement that \"One Mysterious Night is about 1940s crime films,\" indicating the context indeed aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context indicating that \"One Mysterious Night\" is about 1940s crime films.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}